Mandeep Singh

New Delhi9999340849im@msingh.me

mSingh.me

Startups Developer, Laravel Expert, Full Stack Developer, Freelance Architect & IT Consultant

Summary

I've been a freelancer for last 6+ years and have done several kinds of projects. Most of them have been for early stage startups or internal management tools and recently I joined a startup in hyper local grocery delivery genre.

I've been a Laravel Framework developer from last 3 years and have worked on many other technologies like AngularJS, MongoDB, a bit of Python and a bit tweaking in almost all sorts of languages. The kind of jobs that I have done in past 5 years have grown my skills so that languages doesn't matter to me anymore. I pretty much can work on anything.

Work History

Consultant Technical Architect

Feb 2016 - Present

KartRocket

KartRocket provides a power-packed, flexible, simple to use and end-to-end e-commerce platform on a SaaS model to anyone who is looking for a branded online presence. KartRocket unifies the customer experience by providing all required integrations for entering the e-commerce ecosystem (payments, logistics, marketing, discovery & design) in a single self-service portal.

Development Lead

Dec 2015 - Feb 2016

TheSmartTrolley.com

The Smart Trolley is a modern hyper local e-grocery platform to cater to Delhi & NCR. Right from your everyday staples like dals, cereals and flour, to health food, to cakes and bake – if there's any household product or equipment that you have on your mind, you'll find it at The Smart Trolley.com.

Senior Web Developer

Jun 2015 - Aug 2015

BetterButter.in

BetterButter is the most fun and personal way to discover recipes in India!....

Founder & Lead PHP Developer

Nov 2012 - Present

WebsterFolks

WebsterFolks.com is a developement agency specialised in Laravel based projects. It has helped over 400 clients so far to help build their startups or websites.

Freelance Web Developer

Mar 2013 - Present

Envato Stuio

Envato Studio is a community of hand-picked designers, developers and digital talent, available to work on your project. From logo design to web development, to video production, we make it easy to connect and work together to get your job done.

Freelace WordPress Specialist

Aug 2012 - Jun 2015

Elto.com

Elto.com is a curated marketplace of developers and marketers helping small business grow online.

Elto got Acquired by GoDaddy in 2015 and is now known as Godaddy Pro Marketplace.

Freelance Web Developer

May 2012 - Jun 2014

Envato Market

Envato Market is home to thousands of talented designers, developers and creators of all kinds, who sell a huge range of digital goods and assets. There's everything from photographs to project files, sound effects to video templates.

Freelance Web Developer

Mar 2012 - Dec 2012

Fiverr.com

The marketplace for creative & professional services

Freelance Web Developer

Jun 2009 - Jan 2012

Have been doing freelance development for several years for local as well as international clients.

Skills							
JKII	Project Management						
	Laravel PHP Framework						
	Codeigniter PHP Framework						
	Team Managment						
	Lumen PHP Framework						
	Database Designing						
	RESTful API's						
	Amazon Web Services						
	PHP						
	AngularJS						
	Python						

Education

Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA -- Currently Pursuing)

2015 - 2018

Sikkim Manipal University - Distance Education

Senior School (Class 11 & 12)	2005 - 2007
Shri Guru Harkishan Sen Sec School	
High School (Class 10)	1994 - 2005
Daffodil Public High School	